<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fireflies platform development docs</title>
    <link>http://Study-Abroad-App.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fireflies platform development docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 16:21:30 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://Study-Abroad-App.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Update 13 Oct 21</title>
      <link>http://Study-Abroad-App.github.io/posts/update-13-oct-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 16:21:30 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://Study-Abroad-App.github.io/posts/update-13-oct-21/</guid>
      <description>Update 13 Oct Summary  Functional testing of mentor registration complete Showcase of mentor/user registration will be done this weekend Mentor listing and profile are functional  Current features in dev  Chatroom request in dev Community section planning for frontend Server security and database maintenance  Notes  Need to create more BE requirements Need more hands on FE tasks (esp design) Look into handling user-uploaded files &amp;amp; images  Written by Ha Nguyen, 13 Oct</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 29 Aug 21</title>
      <link>http://Study-Abroad-App.github.io/posts/update-29-aug-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 13:45:55 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://Study-Abroad-App.github.io/posts/update-29-aug-21/</guid>
      <description>Update 29 Aug Summary  Aiming to do functional testing &amp;amp; showcase of mentor registration &amp;amp; profile features in 2 weeks Security for registration and private pages will be gradually enforced Project is now named Fireflies  Current features in dev  Mentor registration for invited users Mentor listing &amp;amp; profile display for all visitors Backend security  Notes  Email verification during registration with Amazon SES Get features to function first before adjusting based on figma design How to set up redis server for backend security and also testing Get started on documenting backend APIs Monthly update now  Written by Ha Nguyen, 8 Aug</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting the technical doc site</title>
      <link>http://Study-Abroad-App.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 17:19:30 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://Study-Abroad-App.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Technical doc site is live! What is it about? This site aims to give readers an overview of the features being developed for the SAapp project (name tbc), as well as update current and prospective team members on technical progress and benchmarks. Hopefully will facilitate communication between the different roles within the team (backend, frontend, devops).
SAapp project This project includes building and running a platform for student consultancy and networking among university alumnus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
